# Rajendra Rakha Arya Prabaswara

Malang, Jawa Timur | Politeknik Negeri Malang | 089631565880 | rajendra.rakha29@gmail.com | Linkedin | https://rjndrkha.github.io/



#### Introduction

Hello, I'm Rajendra, 21 years old, from Malang. I am a student from Polytechnic Negeri Malang. I graduated from D4 Informatics Engineering. I am interested in the IT field and I have the ability to Develop Websites and Android Applications. During college, I was active in organizations. I am a very ambitious person, I am very hardworking and can work in a team and I can work under pressure.

#### **Education**

Politeknik Negeri Malang – Malang, Indonesia Diploma IV of Informatics Engineering (International Class) GPA: 3,80	(2019 – 2023)
Republic Polytechnic – Woodlands, Singapore Credit Transfer Internet Of Things Score : A	(2022 – 2022)
<b>Shandong University of Science and Technology – Tiongkok</b> Online Chinese language course	(2020 – 2020)
SMA Islam Malang – Malang,Indonesia Senior High School major of Science	(2016 – 2019)

### Experience-

### **UD Ceker Balap Dampit, Malang**

(2019-2022)

Part Time

- Managing In and Out of stock supply
- Helping to clean up stock supply
- Helping drivers take stock supply at warehouse

## Politeknik Negeri Malang

Student Activities

### • Dewan Perwakilan Mahasiswa

Member Komisi III (Student Aspiration and Research)

#### Workshop Riset Informatika

Member Game Development Class

#### • Internal Competition JTI

Participant Application Innovation Competition Category

## • Pekan Kreativitas Mahasiswa

- Participant Karya Cipta Competition Category
- Online Course Training Setification

#### **DTS VSGA Kominfo**

Kementerian Komunikasi dan Informatika

• Junior Android Development Training 2021

### **Head Division of Sekbid Keorganisasian (OSIS)**

(2016-2018)

SMA Islam Malang

#### **Hard Skill**

- Website & Android Development (Advance)
- Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Visio (Advance)
- Cloud Enginnering (Intermediate)
- UI/UX Design (Intermediate)
- Video Editor (Intermediate)
- English Language (Intermediate)

## **Soft Skill**

- Leadership
- Adaptation
- Managing time
- Creativity
- Problem solving
- Collaboration

## License & Certification

- <u>Junior Android Developer (BNSP)</u> **2021**
- Master Website Development with Laravel 8 (Udemy) 2021
- <u>Develop Website With Wordpress (Udemy)</u> **2021**
- Amazon Certified Cloud Practitioner AWS Cloud (Dicoding) 2021
- Whitesec Org Android Hacking Beginners with Metaexploit (Udemy) 2021
- Machine Learning in Python (Udemy) 2021
- <u>Java Web Services (Udemy)</u> 2021
- Oracle Cloud Infrastructure Certified Foundation Associate (Oracle) 2021
- Automating Infrastructure with Terraform (Google Cloud) 2022
- Build Apps & Websites with Firebase (Google Cloud) 2022
- Build and Secure Networks (Google Cloud) 2022
- Google Cloud's Operations Suite (Google Cloud) 2022

#### Awards and Honors-

#### **JuaraGCP Season 7 - 2022**

Google Cloud Developer Indonesia

## Best Critical Thingking & Programming - 2021

Politeknik Negeri Malang



- Fullstack Application XploreBromo 2021
   Politeknik Negeri Malang
- R'Apps All in One Tools 2021 VSGA KOMINFO
- Personal Website 2021
   Politeknik Negeri Malang
- Flutter Travel Apps 2021 Online Course Learning
- Flutter Cari Kos Apps 2021 Online Course Learning
- ArJ Movie Website 2020
   Politeknik Negeri Malang

## **EMAIL APPLICATION LETTER FRONTEND DEVELOPER - GOJEK**

#### RAJENDRA RAKHA ARYA PRABASWARA

FRONTEND ANDROID & WEBSITE DEVELOPER

Malang, Jawa Timur | 089631565880 | rajendra.rakha29@gmail.com

Malang, 09/03/2022

Mr.Andi Haikal Pratama Human Resources Division PT. Aplikasi Karya Anak Bangsa (Gojek) Jl. Iskandarsyah II No.07, RW 02, Melawai,12160 Kota Jakarta Selatan

Dear Mr. Andi Haikal,

I contacted you regarding the Frontend Developer position post that I found on career.gojek.com. I am very interested in this position and would appreciate your consideration as a candidate for the role. I have experience as a Frontend Website & Android Developer. I'm also certified by BNSP about Junior Android & Website developer

I believe that my experience in Frontend Developer makes me a suitable candidate for this position. My main strengths that will support my success in this position include:

- I'm certified by BNSP
- I try to be a good problem solver
- I finished the project that was given to me well
- I will work hard in giving good performance to the company

For consideration I also provide additional documents include:

- Curriculum Vitae (CV)
- LINKEDIN PROFILE <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rajendra-rakha">https://www.linkedin.com/in/rajendra-rakha</a>
- PROJECT PORTOFOLIO <a href="https://github.com/ArJ-Group">https://github.com/ArJ-Group</a>

I am a detail and results oriented person, which is very important for success in developing an application/website. I can also work well, both individually and in teams who in this position need to work closely with project managers and other developers. My educational background in Information Technology will also support me to work in this position in terms of understanding application basics.

I appreciate your time in reviewing this letter and look forward to hearing from you regarding the next steps in the hiring process. If you have any questions or need additional information, please don't hesitate to contact me.

Sincerely,

Rajendra Rakha Arya Prabaswara

# APPLICATON FORM GOJEK

## FRONTEND ENGINEER - GoFood



## Frontend Engineer - Gofood

BENGALURU / ENGINEERING - PRODUCT ENGINEERING / PERMANENT

SUBMIT YOUR A	APPLICATION	
3051111 10017		
LinkedIn profile	Your full LinkedIn profile will be shared. <a href="Learn more">Learn more</a>	
Resume/CV*	CV_RAJENDRA RAKH, Success!	
Full name *	Rajendra Rakha Arya Prabaswara	
Email *	rajendra.rakha29@gmail.com	
Phone *	6289631565880	
Current company <sup>4</sup>	* State Polytechnic Malang	
LINKS		
LinkedIn URL	https://www.linkedin.com/in/rajendra-rakha-1b7675196	
GitHub URL	http://github.com/Rjndrkha	
Portfolio URL	http://github.com/ArJ-Group	
ADDITIONAL IN	NFORMATION	
l <u>am</u> a person <u>wt</u> <u>can work</u> in a <u>te</u>	ho is able to think critically, and I am a problem solver, I am a very hard worker and also I am	
	Aku manusia hCaptcha Privati - Retentuan	
	SUBMIT APPLICATION	
	Gojek Home Page	
	Jobs powered by LEVER	